<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>3.0.0</latestVersion>
    <url>https://github.com/steve1316/uma-android-automation/releases</url>
    <releaseNotes>
v3.0.0 - Changelog

New
---
- Major overhaul to training algorithm! Now smarter at hitting ideal stats and choosing the best training.
- Added support for stat target customization per race distance.
- Added an option to focus on getting Speed, Stamina and Power to 600+ for the best chance of a 3* Spark.
- Added an option to always do extra races when available. Looking at you, Haru Urara.
- Show more in-depth info in the text log, including stat targets and current settings.
- Added support to focus on leveling up bond levels during the Junior Year phase.
- Training now avoids working on stats that are already maxed (optional toggle).
- Tracks current turn, year, and phase.
- Added an option to not retry failed mandatory races (optional toggle).
- New setting category for racing-specific options.

Adjustments
---
- Improved accuracy when reading stat gains and mood from the screen.
- Sped up many processes with multithreading (training analysis, stat reading, etc.).
- Better scoring for training options, especially when rainbows or skill hints are involved.
- Updated stat prioritization default (Wit now above Guts in priority).
- Improved behavior when races aren't available (falls back to other actions).
- Delay adjustments for smoother automation.
- More robust detection of race types, stat limits, and training contexts.

Fixed
---
- Fixed a bug where the bot wouldn't race due to maiden race popups or low fan count.
- Fixed typo in settings (Wits to Wit).
- Fixed crashes related to empty strings in dialog inputs.
- Resolved tap issues on extra race selection and other UI elements.
- Fixed issues with parsing fan amounts and visible characters/supports.
- Improved stability when the service is manually stopped or fails mid-task.
- Fix possible crashes due to concurrent modifications to the MessageLog and the Accessibility Service not being ready.

    </releaseNotes>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>